Guide to the Yale College Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Grades and enrollment data, 1957-2007; Accession 2016-A-050
  - Yale College 2009 Fall Grades
    - Music, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Music School, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Philosophy, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Physics, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Political Science, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Psychology, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Sociology, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Spanish, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Special Term Course, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Statistics, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Teacher prep, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Theater Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Peking University, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Yale College 2010 Spring Grades
    - Accounting, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - African American Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - African Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Anthropology, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - American Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Arabic, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Applied Physics, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Archaeological Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Architecture., 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Art, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Astronomy, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Chronic Disease Epidemiology, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Chemistry, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Chinese, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Classic Civilization, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - College Seminars, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Cognitive Science, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Computer Science, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Comparative Literature, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Computing and the Arts, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Drama, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Economics, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - English, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Environmental Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Ethics, Politics Economics, Spring 2010 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Epidemiology/Public Health, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 188a)
    - Ethnicity, Race, Migration, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - Film, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - French, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - German, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - German Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Health Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - History, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - History of Art, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Health Public Adminstration, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Humanities, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Indonesian, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - International Relations, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - International Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Italian, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Korean, Spring2010 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Law, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - Latin American Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - Linguistics, Spring2010 (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Literature, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Management, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - Math, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 211)
    - Molecular, Biophysics Biochemistry, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Modern Middle East Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - Music, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 215)
    - School of Music, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 216)
    - Near Eastern Language Civilization, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 217)
    - Philosophy, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 218)
    - Physics, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 219)
    - Political Science, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 220)
    - Portuguese, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 221)
    - Psychology, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 222)
    - Sociology, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 223)
    - Religious Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 224)
    - Science, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 225)
    - South Asian Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 226)
    - Spanish, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 227)
    - Statistics, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 228)
    - Theater Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 229)
    - Vienamese, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 230)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2010 Spring (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - Yale College Corporation Degrees
    - 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 1988 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 1999 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 1997 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 2003 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - 1999 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - 1996 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - 1989 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - 1988 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Yale College Major Lists
    - Approved Majors-Architecture, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics Majors, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Studies, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Global Affairs Majors, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Major Statistics 1997-98, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Major Statistics 1994-95, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Major Statistics 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Major Statistics 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Majors (Final) 11/1/1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Majors 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Residential College Major Lists, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Major Statistics, November 1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Major Statistics 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Major Statistics 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Major Statistics 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Major Statistics 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Major Statistics 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Major Statistics 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1967 (Tentative) 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Majors (Final) 11/1/1957 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Majors (Final) 11/1/1958 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Majors (Final) 11/1/1959 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Major Statistics 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Major Statistics 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Major Statistics 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Class of 1972 Tentative Major Statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Class of 1964 (Final), 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1975 Tentative Majors (August 1972) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Class of 1976 Tentative majors for 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Major Statistics 12/70, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Class of 1973-Tentative Major Statistics 8/7/70, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Tentative Majors for 1971-1972, Class of 1974 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Major Statistics 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Major Statistics 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Major Statistics 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Major Statistics 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Major Statistics 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Major Statistics 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Major Statistics 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Major Statistics 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Major Statistics 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Major Statistics 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Major Statistics 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Major Statistics 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Major Statistics 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Major Statistics 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Major Statistics 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Major Statistics 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Major Statistics 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Majors (Final) 11/1/1963 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Class of 1965 Final (1963-1964) (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Class of 1966 (Tentative) 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Class of 1966, Final (1964-1965) (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Tentative Major Statistics, Class of 1966 (1965-1966) (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Tentative Major Statistics, (1965-1966) Class of 1968 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Tentative Major, Class of 1971, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Class of 1970, Tentative Majors, June 1967 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Tentative Statistics, Class of 1969, May 1966 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Class of 1965 (Tentative), 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Class of 1964 (Tentative), 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Class of 1963 (1961-1962) (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Class of 1963 (Tentative), 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Class of 1962 (1960-1961) (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Class of 1962 (1959-1960), Tentative (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Majors (Final) 11/1/1961 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Class of 1961 (1958-1959 Tentative) (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Class of 1961 (1959-1960) (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Majors (Final) 11/1/1960 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Class of 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Class of 1960 (1958-1959) (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Class of 1960, (1957-1958), Tentative (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Class of 1959 (1958-1959) (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Class of 1959 (1956-1957), Tentative (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Class of 1959 (1957-1958) (Box 4, Folder 73a)
    - Class of 1958 (1957-1958) (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Class of 1958 (1956-1957) (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Class of 1958 (1955-1956) Tentative (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Class of 1957 (1955-1956) (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Major Subjects, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Class of 1957, (1954-1955) Tentative (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Class of 1956 (1954-1955) (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Class of 1955 (1953-1954) (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Class of 1956 (1953-1954) Tentative (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Yale College Miscellaneous Files
    - Yale-China (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Accident Report Blanks (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Postage meter Equipment (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Academic Record Requests (Yale-China) (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Weekly Memos 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Faculty Advisors 1992 (Class of 1996) (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Weekly Memos 1999 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Phelp's Association (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Exceptional Distinction in the major 91-96 (Box 4, Folder 91-92)
    - Distinction in major, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 92a)
  - Transcript Elections for Yale College Summer Session
    - 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - 2004 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - 2005 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - 2006 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - 2007 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - 2008 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - 2009 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Yale College 2010 Fall Grades
    - Distributional Requirement, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - American Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Accounting, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - African American Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - American Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Applied Mathematics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Anthropology, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Applied Physics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Arabic, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Architecture, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Art, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Astronomy, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Chemistry, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Chinese, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Classical Civilization, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Cognitive Science, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - College Seminars, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Computer Science, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Calhoun College Seminar, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Davenport College Seminar, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Morse College Seminar, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Directed Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - East Asian Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Economics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Engineering Accredited Degrees, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Epidemiology of Microbial Disease, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - English, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Enginineering Applied Science, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Environmental Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 134a)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Ethnicity, Race, Migration, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Environmental Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Film Media Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - French, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Geology Geophysics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - German, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Health Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - History, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - History of Art, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Humanities, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - International Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Italian, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Japanese, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Latin, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Law, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Literature, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Mathematics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biolology, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Management, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Modern Middle East Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Music, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Near Eastern Language Civilization, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Philosophy, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Physics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Political Science, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Psychology, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Religion, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Religious Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Russian East Europe Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Russian, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Sociology, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Spanish, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Statistics, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Kiswahili, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Theater Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Peking University, 2010 Fall (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Yale College 2011 Spring Grades
    - Accounting, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - African American Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - African Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - American Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Anthropology, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Applied Physics, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Arabic, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Architecture, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Art, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Astronomy, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Cell Biology, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Chronic Disease Epidemiology, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Chemistry, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Chinese, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Cognitive Science, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Classic Civilization, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - College Seminars, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Computer Science, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Directed Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - East Asian Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
    - Economics, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Epidemiology of Microbial Disease, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - English, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Environmental Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Film Media Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - French, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - German, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Greek, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - History, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - History of Art, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Humanities, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - International Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Italian, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Japanese, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Latin, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Law, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Linguistics, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Literature, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Math, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Management, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Modern Middle East Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Modern Middle East Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Music Department, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Operation Research, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Philosophy, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Physics, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Peking University, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Political Science, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Psychology, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Religious Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Russian East Europe Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Sociology, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Spanish, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Special Term Course, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Statistics, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Theater Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Vietnanese, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2011 Spring (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Yale College 2007 Fall Grades
    - Distributional Requirements, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Accounting, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - African American Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - African Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - American Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Anthropology, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Applied Math, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Archaeological Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Architecture, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Art, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Biological Engineering, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Chemistry, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Chinese, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Classical Civilization, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Cognitive Science, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - College Seminars, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Computer Science, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - The DeVane Lecture Course, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Directed Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - East Asian Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Economics, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Egyptian, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - English, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Ethnicity, Race, Migration, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Environmental Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Film Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - French, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - German, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - History, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - History of Art, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Health Policy Administration, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Humanities, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - International Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Japanese, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Latin, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Law, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Literature, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Management, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Math, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Molecular, Biophysics Biochemistry, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Music, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Nursing, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Philosophy, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Physics, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Political Science, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Psychology, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Quantitative Reasoning, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Religious Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Russian, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Sociology, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Spanish, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Special Term Course, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Statistics, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Theater Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Vietnamese, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Yale College 2008 Spring Grades
    - African American Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - African Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 140)